Clark W. Thompson papers, Inclusive: 1931-1966, undated, Bulk: 1959-1966
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Departments, 1955-1966; 4
  - Post Office, Mont Belview, Nursery, New Ulm, and Orchard, 1959-1962 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Post Office, Pattison, Pierce, Pledger, and Point Comfort, 1958-1962 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Post Office, Port Bolivar, Port Lavaca, Rosenberg, and Rosharon, 1959-1962 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Post Office, Sugar Land, Sweeny, and Victoria, 1960-1965 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Post Office, Wallis, Weimer, Weesatche, and Wharton, 1959-1961 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Post Office, Winnie and Yoakum, 1958-1961 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - State, General, 1962 November-1963 March (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - State, General, 1963 April-August (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - State, General, 1963 September-December (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - State, General, 1964 January-March (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - State, General, 1964 April-November (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - State, General, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - State, General, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - State, Agency for International Development, 1962 December-1963 September (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - State, Agency for International Development, 1963 November-1964 October (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - State, Agency for International Development, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - State, Arms Control and Disarmament, 1962-1964 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - State, Cuba, 1963 February-March (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - State, Cuba, 1963 April-September (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - State, Cyprus, 1964 August (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - State, Letters from Ambassadors, 1965 August (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - State, Notifications of Travel Plans, 1963-1966 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - State, Peace Corps, 1962-1964 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - State, Russian Wheat Deal, 1963-1964 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - State, Vietnam, 1963-1966 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - State, Visa Requests, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Treasury, General, 1961-1963 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Treasury, General, 1964 January-April (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Treasury, General, 1964 May-December (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Treasury, General, 1965-1966 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Treasury, Coast Guard, 1958-1961 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Treasury, Coast Guard, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Treasury, Coast Guard, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Treasury, Coast Guard, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Treasury, Coast Guard, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Treasury, Customs Bureau, 1960-1962 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Treasury, Customs Bureau, 1963-1964 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Treasury, Customs Bureau, 1965-1966 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Treasury, Internal Revenue Service, 1962 October-1963 July (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Treasury, Internal Revenue Service, 1963 August-December (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Treasury, Internal Revenue Service, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Treasury, Internal Revenue Service, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Treasury, Internal Revenue Service, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Veterans Affairs, General, 1960-1961 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Veterans Affairs, General, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Veterans Affairs, General, 1964-1965 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Veterans Affairs, Closing of VA Hospitals, 1965 January-February (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Veterans Affairs, Closing of VA Hospitals, 1965 March-June (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Veterans Affairs, Compensation Applications, 1956-1963 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Veterans Affairs, Pension Bills, 1965-1966 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Legislative, 1931-1966; 5
  Series V. Legislative includes general files, bills, legislation, speeches, voting records, and news releases for most of Thompson’s congressional terms. These materials are arranged according to Congressional session. The bulk of these materials comes from Thompson’s service in the 87th, 88th, and 89th Congresses (the 1960's).
  There are several folders that contain information on the Panama Canal, one of Thompson’s legislative focal points. Materials from three decades - spanning the 1940's to the 1960's - relating to the administration of, proposed expansions to, and maintenance of the canal are present. Issues of the "Congressional Record" and various reports are arranged by topic, while folders containing bills, correspondence, and newspaper clippings are all arranged chronologically. The series is in good condition.
  - Speeches, 1947-1948 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Voting Records, 1953-1954 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - H.R. 58, 1954 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Voting Records, 1955-1956 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Voting Records, 1957-1958 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Congressional District Atlas, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - H.R. 9969, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - News Releases, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Campaign Expenditures, undated (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Congressional District Data Book, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Extension of Remarks, 1961-1962 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Liaison Offices, 1961-1962 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Voting Records, 1961-1962 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - H.J. 191, Equal Rights, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - H.R. 2325, Columbus Bend project, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - H.R. 2529, Civil Service Retirement Act, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - H.R. 3689, Rice Production, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - H.R. 4626, Vessels of the United States, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - H.R. 6546, Agriculture, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - H.R. 8320, Freeport Harbor project, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - H.R. 8467, Wallisville Dam and Reservoir, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - H.R. 8593, Agricultural Act amendment, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - H.R. 8911, Immigration, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - H.R. 9013, Agriculture, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - S. 1740, Truth in Lending" bill, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - H.J. 853, Agriculture, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - H.R. 234, Excise Tax, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - H.R. 507, House committee decisions, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - H.R. 8952, Excise tax, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - H.R. 10223, Internal Revenue Code, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - H.R. 10928, Tariff Act, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - H.R. 11446, National security, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - H.R. 13288 (1 of 3), Armed Services, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - H.R. 13288 (2 of 3), Armed Services, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - H.R. 13288 (3 of 3), Armed Services, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - News Releases, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - News Releases, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Barry Goldwater, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, Constituents about Legislation (1 of 4), 1963 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, Constituents about Legislation (2 of 4), 1963 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, Constituents about Legislation (3 of 4), 1963 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Constituents about Legislation (4 of 4), 1963 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Constituents about Legislation, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Fair Labor Amendment History, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Federal Excise Tax Report, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - News Releases, 1963 January-May (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - News Releases, 1963 June-November (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - News Releases, 1963 December (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - News Releases, 1964 January-May (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - News Releases, 1964 June-December (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Speech, Dallas Rotary Club, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Speech, David Lawrence to Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) Academy, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Speech, Galveston Rotary Club, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Speech, ILA Meeting, 64 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Speech, Soil Conservation Service, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Voting Records, 1963-1964 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - H.J. 192, Agriculture, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - H.J. 330, Equal Rights, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - H.R. 17, Columbus Bend project, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - H.R. 1017, Automotive industry, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - H.R. 1018, Inheritance, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - H.R. 1156, Palmetto Bend project, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - H.R. 1234, Immigration, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - H.R. 1574, Immigration, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - H.R. 3742 (1 of 2), Agriculture, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - H.R. 3742 (1 of 2), Agriculture, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - H.R. 4772, Immigration, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - H.R. 5693 (1 of 5), Antidumping Act, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - H.R. 5693 (2 of 5), Antidumping Act, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - H.R. 5693 (3 of 5), Antidumping Act, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - H.R. 5693 (4 of 5), Antidumping Act, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - H.R. 5693 (5 of 5), Antidumping Act, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - H.R. 5925, Internal Revenue Code, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - H.R. 6178, Internal Revenue Code, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - H.R. 6467, Tariff Act, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - H.R. 6466, Internal Revenue Code, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - H.R. 6620 (1 of 2), Social Security Act, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - H.R. 6620 (2 of 2), Social Security Act, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - H.R. 6654 (1 of 2), NASA, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - H.R. 6654 (2 of 2), NASA, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - H.R. 7741, Internal Revenue Code, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - H.R. 8026, Internal Revenue Code, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - H.R. 8232, Tariff Classification Act, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - H.R. 8563, Interoceanic Canals Commission, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - H.R. 8798, Internal revenue Code, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - H.R. 9167, Internal Revenue Code, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - S. 1576, Public Health Service Act, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - H.R. 1839, Tariff Act, 1964 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - H.R. 10256, Retirement Plans, 1964 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - H.R. 10338, Meat Products Import, 1964 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - H.R. 10832 and H.R. 10834, Antidumping Act, 1964 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Baby Books Sent, 1965-1966 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Congressional Club Cookbook, 1965-1966 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Constituents about Legislation (1 of 2), 1965 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Constituents about Legislation (2 of 2), 1965 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Constituents about Legislation (1 of 2), 1966 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Constituents about Legislation (2 of 2), 1966 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Extension of Remarks, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Hearings on Florence and Beirut Agreements, 1966 June (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - News Releases, 1965-1966 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Speech, Victoria, Texas, 1965 April 25 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Speech, Marine Corps Reserve Officers Association, 1966 May 13 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Voting Record, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - United States International Trade Administration Report on Excise Tax, 1965 January (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - H.J. 102, Population, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - H.J. 592, Equal Rights, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - H.J. 827, Southwest border area, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - H.R. 1, Hospital insurance program, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - H.R.162, Columbus Bend project, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - H.R. 163, Palmetto Bend project, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - H.R. 186, Committee Appointments, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - H.R. 189, Federal Aviation Act, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - H.R. 2353, Immigration, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - H.R. 2576, Immigration, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - H.R. 4287, Domestic Industries Security Act, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - H.R. 4342, Immigration, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - H.R. 4304, Congressional Medal of Honor, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - H.R. 4343, Immigration, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - H.R. 4286, Social Security Act, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - H.R. 4814, Property inheritance, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - H.R. 4933, Immigration, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - H.R. 7374, Internal revenue Code, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - H.R. 7380, Immigration, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - H.R. 8512, Antidumping Act, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - H.R. 8876, Immigration, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - H.R. 9883, Internal Revenue Code, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - H.R. 10625, Uniformed Services retirement pay, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - H.R. 10138, Department of Marine and Atmospheric Affairs, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - H.R. 10661, Immigration, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - H.R. 11659, Post Office, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - H.R. 12052, Special postal stamp, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - H.R. 13678, Internal Revenue Code, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - H.R. 14154 (1 of 2), Tariff Schedules, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - H.R. 14154 (2 of 2), Tariff Schedules, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - H.R. 15477, Palmetto Bend projects, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - H.R. 15795, Federal estate tax, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - H.R. 16488, Pollution Abatement Incentive Act, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - H.R. 17041, Real estate, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - H.R. 17309, Educational expenses of teachers, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - General, Armed Forces Talk 373, 1951 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - General, Background Materials, 1946-1950 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - General, Background Materials, 1951-1953 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - General, Background Materials, 1954 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - General, Background Materials, 1955 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - General, Background Materials, 1956 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - General, Background Materials (1 of 3), 1957 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - General, Background Materials (2 of 3), 1957 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - General, Background Materials (3 of 3), 1957 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - General, Background Materials (1 of 2), 1958-1960 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - General, Background Materials (2 of 2), 1958-1960 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - General, Committee on Tolls, 1948 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - General, Committee on Tolls, 1949 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - General, Committee on Tolls, 1950 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - General, Correspondence, 1948 November-1949 May (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - General, Correspondence, 1949 June-August (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - General, Correspondence, 1949 September-December (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - General, Correspondence, 1950-1953 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - General, Correspondence and Legislation, 1948-1956 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - General, Extension of Remarks of Clark Thompson, 1950 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - General, Extension of Remarks of Schuyler Otis Bland, 1949 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - General, Memorandums Regarding the Panama Canal, 1951-1964 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - General, National Federation of American Shipping, Inc., 1948 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - General, Panama Canal Engineers, 1949 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - General, Press Releases, 1947 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - General, Proclamations by the President, 1948-1949 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - General, Problems and Proposals, 1931-1951 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - General, Travel and Supply Expenses, 1949 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - General, Pacific American Steamship Association, 1950 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - General, Various Acts from Executive Office of the Panama Canal, 1946-1947 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - "Congressional Record", 80th Congress, 1st Session, 1947 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - "Congressional Record", 80th Congress, 2nd Session, 1948 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - "Congressional Record", 81st Congress, 1st Session (1 of 2), 1949 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - "Congressional Record", 81st Congress, 1st Session (2 of 2), 1949 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - "Congressional Record", 81st Congress, 2nd Session, 1950 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - "Congressional Record", 82nd Congress, 1st Session, 1951 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - "Congressional Record", 83rd Congress, 1st Session, 1953 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - "Congressional Record", 83rd Congress, 2nd Session, 1954 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - "Congressional Record", 84th Congress, 1st Session, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - "Congressional Record", 88th Congress, 1st Session, 1963 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - "Congressional Record", 88th Congress, 2nd Session, 1964 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - "Congressional Record", Federal Register, Volume 15, Number 27, 1950 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - "Congressional Record", Reports, History of the Canal Zone, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Reports, Board of Consulting Engineers for the Panama Canal, 1947 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Reports, The Governor of the Panama Canal, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Reports, The Governor of the Panama Canal, 1947 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Reports, Pursuant to H.R. 36, 1947 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Reports, Subcommittee Report on Inspection of Panama Canal Operations and Facilities, 1948 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Reports, Presentation of the Hoover Medal to Malcolm Pirnie, 1949 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Reports, Accountant’s Informal Report to the Sub-Committee on the Panama Canal, 1949 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Reports, Bureau of the Budget, Panama Canal and Panama Railroad Company, 1949-1950 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Reports, Activities of the Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee, 1951 (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - Reports, Report on Audit of Panama Canal and Canal Zone Government, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - Reports, Special Analysis by the American Enterprise Institute, 1964 (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - H.R. 5417, Panama Canal, 1937 (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - H.R. 3629, Panama Canal, 1947 (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - H.R. 4833, Interoceanic Canals Commission, 1948 (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - Fisheries Stabilization Act, 1949 (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - H.R. 3158, 1949 (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - H.R. 44, 1949 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - S. 1489, 1949 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - H.R. 5461, 1949 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - S. 1136, 1949 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Interoceanic Canals Commission Act, 1949 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - S. 3649, Panama Canal, 1950 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - S. 3657, Rivers and harbors, 1950 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - S. 3650, Panama Canal, 1950 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - H.R. 8677 (1 of 2), Canal Zone Code, 1950 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - H.R. 8677 (2 of 2), Canal Zone Code, 1950 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - S.J.R. 166, Construction reserve funds, 1952 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - H.R. 8457, Interoceanic Canals Commission, 1952 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - H.R. 8458, Interoceanic Canals Commission, 1952 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - H.R. 3335, Interoceanic Canals Commission, 1955 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - H.R. 3258, Interoceanic Canals Commission, 1957 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Committee on Merchant Marine and Fisheries, 1947 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Subcommittee on Panama Canal, 1948 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Subcommittee on Panama Canal (1 of 2), 1949 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Subcommittee on Panama Canal (2 of 2), 1949 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Subcommittee on Panama Canal (1 of 3), 1950 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Subcommittee on Panama Canal (2 of 3), 1950 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Subcommittee on Panama Canal (3 of 3), 1950 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Subcommittee on Panama Canal, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - General Correspondence, 1952 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Subcommittee on Panama Canal, 1953 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Subcommittee on Panama Canal, 1954 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Subcommittee on Panama Canal, 1955 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - General Correspondence, 1956 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - General Correspondence, 1963 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - General Correspondence, 1964 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Journal Articles, 1947 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Journal Articles, 1948 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Journal Articles, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Journal Articles, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Journal Articles, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Journal Articles, 1952 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Journal Articles, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Journal Articles, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Journal Articles, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Journal Articles, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Personal, 1933-1965, undated; 6
  Series VI. Personal is moderately-sized and consists of three primary types of materials: administrative, correspondence, and campaign. The administrative materials contain alphabetical office records from the 1960's, Thompson’s final decade in office. Most of these records pertain to office equipment and personnel.
  The correspondence within this series is comprised primarily of invitations accepted by Clark Thompson from the late 1950's and early 1960's, highlighting the varied events attended by one of Washington’s most sought-after and well-connected socialites. At the time, the influence of Clark and his wife Libbie was such that their home was often referred to as the “Texas Embassy.” In addition to invitations, there are also wide-ranging conversations with constituents and informants from his congressional district that kept him abreast of important developments back home.
  The campaign materials recount Thompson’s first foray as a U.S. Representative in 1933 as well as his subsequent campaigns for political office from 1948 to 1964. These folders are arranged by date. The series also contains numerous folders on significant developments within the Democratic Party as well as national and Texan politics. The series is in good condition.
  - Office Records, Equipment, 1961-1963 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Office Records, Equipment, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Office Records, Equipment, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Office Records, Expenses Form, undated (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Office Records, Patronage, 1964-1965 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Office Records, Personnel, 1962-1965 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Office Records, Stationery, 1963-1965 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Office Records, Telephone and Telegraph, 1962-1965 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - General, 1959-1966 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Appreciation Dinner (1 of 2), 1963-1964 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Appreciation Dinner (2 of 2), 1963-1964 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Army-Navy Game, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Bauer, William "Bill" H., 1958-1959 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Bosl, Florence, 1959 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Bradshaw, Truman, 1958-1959 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Capsin, Joseph, 1959-1961 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Capsin, Joseph, 1962-1963 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Capsin, Joseph, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Capsin, Joseph, 1965 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Cunningham, David, 1962-1964 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Dazey, William, 1958-1961 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Ford, Fred, 1957-1958 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Goedecke, Otto, 1959-1962 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Invitations, 1960-1961 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Invitations, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Invitations, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Invitations, 1964 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Invitations, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Invitations, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Luther, Charles, 1958-1960 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Luther, Charles, 1961-1962 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Lykes, Joseph T., 1961 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Publications Received, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Publications Received (1 of 2), 1966 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Publications Received (2 of 2), 1966 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - 1933 Campaign, Data and Expenses (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - 1940 Campaign, Mansfield Campaign (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - 1948 Campaign, General (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - 1948 Campaign, Campaign Publicity, 1947 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - 1948 Campaign, Data and Expenses (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - 1950 Campaign, General, 1950-1951 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - 1950 Campaign, Campaign Publicity (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - 1950 Campaign, Data and Expenses (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - 1950 Campaign, Correspondence (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - 1950 Campaign, Radio Scripts (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - 1952 Campaign, Bills and Statements (1 of 2) (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - 1952 Campaign, Bills and Statements (2 of 2) (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - 1952 Campaign, Proofs and Materials (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - 1952 Campaign, Congratulatory Letters (1 of 2) (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - 1952 Campaign, Congratulatory Letters (2 of 2) (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - 1952 Campaign, Correspondence (1 of 5) (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - 1952 Campaign, Correspondence (2 of 5) (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - 1952 Campaign, Correspondence (3 of 5) (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - 1952 Campaign, Correspondence (4 of 5) (Box 57, Folder 5)